{
    "subject": "resource/Asya_(singer)",
    "predicate": "property/alternativeNames",
    "object": "T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan",
    "human_readable": "Asya's alternative name is T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9791572093963623,
            "question": "Is T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan another name for Asya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8902484178543091,
            "question": "Who is T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8502870202064514,
            "question": "What is Asya's alternative name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8373183012008667,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Asya and T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7571830153465271,
            "question": "Can you provide an alternative name for Asya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7506693005561829,
            "question": "What is the full name of Asya's alternative identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6951906085014343,
            "question": "Is 'T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan' a common alias?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5768710970878601,
            "question": "What are the two names associated with Asya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5171800851821899,
            "question": "Does Asya have a different name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4041784703731537,
            "question": "How many names are associated with Asya?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Asya's alternative name is T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1532_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Asya have a different name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1532_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the two names associated with Asya?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1532_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan' a common alias?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1532_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1532_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently refer to an artist known as \"Asya,\" whose legal name is given as \"T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan.\" This information supports the statement that Asya's alternative name is T\u00fclay Ke\u00e7ialan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}